[{"answer": "Well, never mind yours.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Your life?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I think it would have been a good idea.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "It would be good, though, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "ALDWIN: Well, I think that what I want him to do and what I think needs to be done are to some degree separate things but I do know that we've had a lot of programs, government-funded program for years now that represent both sides of the aisle.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What do you want him to do to really show some fulfillment to that promise that we all felt?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I don't think it is washing with the public.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "That's not going to wash with the public, is it?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, I'm in favor of people owning guns but I'm in favor of there being the most arduous process for them to qualify to own that gun.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What is your view and should politicians led by the president be doing more to try to at least limit some form of weapon?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think at best it's 50-50 where there's a rural or semirural component or people who live in a city that's kind of a B-sized city and out West where they have access to rural countrysides and shooting and guns and hunting, that sort of thing, is part of the culture.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "You don't think?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Are you still flirting with it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, because, first of all, I start with looking at the other candidates.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Can your wife not read?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Condi, we are not doing this.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "She's certainly not younger, is she?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "That's him at McDonald's.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Shopping?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, I would imagine that the period -- the grieving period and the acceptance period when it doesn't go your way, especially when there was every inclination that it would go his way and remember what a long torturous, tedious primary period it was.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Is it good for any politician?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I don't think I really do have any conflict with them in the sense that -- that guy, you're talking about that photographer, I mean, I think the most important thing to remember is I did not punch the guy and the guy was overheard by witnesses going down the street going through his camera with his finger, going, yes, there's a one.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Why do you have such conflict with them?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "If I could press the button tomorrow and flush them all down some swirling sewer vortex.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Bing Crosby, Dickens.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Did you bring any of your Schweaty balls for me?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Well, there's things like that but that's the only place you can say it.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Is it a fact that it's mainly live and it's dangerous, that' s it's -- you know?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Well, I think two things.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What can you say about that?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "-- been more properly in love.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Am I gay?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I may be unconsciously.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I think I'm very romantic, yes.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Are you a naturally romantic man?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, I think as we get older, we have a more acute appreciation of that.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Or have you felt this before, but it just didn't work out?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I think I'm --", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Are you a nicer guy to be with?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I think the biggest thing I wanted changed is just how stress filled my life is, because I try to do a lot.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Are you a better partner, do you think?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "I'd say it's probably a tie between my daughter being born.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Putting aside women and children, what's been the moment, if I could relive it for you, you'd go for?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Is that what I said?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Other than women and children?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I will.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Now that I'm not TV anymore, will you still have me on your show?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "You know, in the beginning you don't cope.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "How do you even begin to cope?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I think the only reason why time is a healer is because, you know, my whole life -- or not my whole life but certainly what felt like my whole life up to this point has really been about my girls and my children.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Is time, as people say so often in these situations, any kind of healer?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "My life was fantastic.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "How would you describe life before this happened to you?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I mean, it's so horrific and so awful in that, you know, before this happened to me, I would never have imagined that there was anything that have could stopped me from going into a burning building and to save my children.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "When you're beginning to realize that you can't get your girls or your parents out of this inferno, what was going through your mind?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Oh, god, yes.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Did part of you just wish you died, too?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Do you blame anybody?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "I mean, do you even really know exactly what happened?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Yes, that's right.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Because the house was demolished, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Do you have a satisfactory answer?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Yes, in his retirement.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "He was an in store Santa Claus, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Is that how you feel now?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "You know, every day has been awful.", "docId": "121209pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "What will you do, do you think?", "qSentId": 656}]